

Ahmed Škulj

Software Egineer / Junior Frontend Developer

Details

Address:

Ulica Patriotske Lige 94 Kakanj, 72240 Bosnia and Herzegovina

Phone:

061/957/535

Email:

ahmedskulj10@gmail.com

Github:

https://github.com/ahmedskulj00/

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

SQL

Node.js

C++

Languages

Bosnian

English

About me

A Software Engineer from Bosnia and Herzegovina. I have graduated from University of Zenica, with a Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering. Love to work with front-end technologies. I have already worked as a Junior Software Developer and currently I work as a Junior Frontend Developer, so I have experience in the industry. I'm a hardworking person and I think that only hard work and consistency are keys to success.

Employment History

Junior Software Developer, Mistral Technologies

Aug 2021 - Nov 2021 **Q** Sarajevo

- · Worked with mentor on different tasks in React.
- Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.
- Learned about agile development

Junior Frontend Developer, Purple Key

Dec 2021 - May 2022 Sarajevo

- Worked on different projects using React.
- Learned about different tips and tricks for better development
- Worked on my UX/UI skills

Frontend Developer, Viberate

May 2022 - July 2022 • Remote

- Worked on Viberate app.
- Learned a lot about charts implementation in React
- Learned about PDF exporting in React

Education

Grammar School "Muhsin Rizvić", Kakanj

Software Engineering, University of Zenica

Relevant Projects

Portfolio - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React

Quiz App - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React

Weather App - HTML, CSS, JavaScript